Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Dial1987-1995
      - Spirit soap, 1987-1990
        - 980. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 9243 Gimmie Three Soaps :30. 1990 (Box 55)
      - Spirit soap (continued), 1991-1993 (Box 56)
        - 981. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1865 Gimmie Three Soaps :15. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 982. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1865 Gimmie Three Soaps :15. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 983. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1773 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev. 5 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 984. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1773 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev. 5 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 985. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1773 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev. 5 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 986. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 0633 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev.3 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 987. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 0633 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev.3 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 988. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. 9 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 989. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1743 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev.4 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 990. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. 8 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 991. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1743 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev.4 :30. 1991 (Box 56)
        - 992. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 1773 Gimmie Three Soaps Rev. 5 :30; XYLC 1865 Gimmie Three Soaps :15. 1992 (Box 56)
        - 993. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 3433 Soaps/New Music/CC :30; XYLC 3445 Soaps/New Music/CC :15. 1993 (Box 56)
        - 994. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 3433 Soaps/New Music/CC :30; XYLC 3445 Soaps/New Music/CC :15. 1993 (Box 56)
        - 995. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 3563 Soaps/FSI :30. 1993 (Box 56)
        - 996. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 3563 Soaps/FSI":30. 1993 (Box 56)
      - Spirit soap (continued), 1993-1994 (Box 57)
        - 997. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. XYLC 3433 Soaps/New Music/CC w/1993 Copyright. 1993 (Box 57)
        - 998. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Spirit Soap. Two Sides :30; Sweat :30; Models :30. 1994 (Box 57)
      - Tone soap, 1987-1996
        - 999. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Tone Soap. Tone Presentation. Work Out :15 off-line Edit. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1000. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Tone Soap. Beauty Contest: :30. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1001. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Tone Soap. Work Out :30. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1002. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Tone Soap. Tone Presentation :30 off-line edit. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1003. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Tone Soap. Smart Enough :30. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1004. Dial Tone Soap. Test Super. 4 Spots. 1987 (Box 57)
        - 1005. Gotham Inc. Dial Tone Soap. XYLC 5433 Nature's Gift :30. 1996 (Box 57)
        - 1006. Gotham Inc. Dial Tone Soap. XYLC 5433 Nature's Gift :30. 1996 (Box 57)
        - 1007. Gotham Inc. Dial Tone Soap. XYLC 5433 Nature's Gift :30. 1996 (Box 57)
        - 1008. Gotham Inc. Dial Tone Soap. XYLC 6623 o-ooo-h :30. 1996 (Box 57)
      - Villa Lorenzo foods, 1992-1994 (Box 58)
        - 1009. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 2313 Villa Lorenzo w/Title :30; XYLC 2303 I want my Pasta :30; XYLC 2283 Tarantella :30. 1992 (Box 58)
        - 1010. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3455 Villa Lorenzo :15. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1011. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3423 Villa :30. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1012. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3423 Villa :30. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1013. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3423 Villa/CC :30; XYLC 3483 Villa/Alt./CC :30. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1014. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3455 Villa Lorenzo (CBS/NBC) :15; XYLC 3595 Villa Lorenzo Alt. (ABC) :15. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1015. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3483 Villa/Alt :30. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1016. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3455 Villa Lorenzo (CBS/NBC) :15; XYLC 3595 Villa Lorenzo Alt. (ABC) :15. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1017. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3455 Villa Lorenzo :15. 1993 (Box 58)
        - 1018. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Villa Lorenzo Pasta for one. XYLC 3423 Villa :30; XYLC 3483 Villa/Alt/CC :30. 1994 (Box 58)
      - Multiple Products,1994
        - 1019. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Top That Potato Toppings. Talking Potatoes :30. 1994 (Box 58)
        - 1020. A. Eicoff & Co. Dial. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1994 (Box 58)
    - Drackett,1975-1995 and undated
      - Endust (also a Bristol-Myers product), 1980-1984 (Box 59)
        - 1021. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 0473 Checkmate rev. :30; BMEN 0483 Lifestyle rev. :30. 1980 (Box 59)
        - 1022. Bristol Myers. Endust. Historical Reel, 1973-1980. 8-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 59)
        - 1023. Daniel & Charles. Endust. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1981 (Box 59)
        - 1024. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 1503 Interior Decorator :30. 1981 (Box 59)
        - 1025. Bristol Myers. Daniel & Charles. Endust. BMEN 1503 Interior Decorator :30. 1981 (Box 59)
        - 1026. Laurence Charles and Free. Endust. Vers. 2 :32. 1982 (Box 59)
        - 1027. Laurence Charles and Free. Endust. Vers. 1 :32. 1982 (Box 59)
        - 1027. Laurence Charles and Free. Endust. Wood Veneer. Vers. 2 :32. 1982 (Box 59)
        - 1028. Laurence Charles and Free. Endust. Good Furniture Vers. 1 :32. 1982 (Box 59)
        - 1029. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1983 (Box 59)
        - 1030. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 3563 Interior Decorator II :30. 1983 (Box 59)
        - 1031. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 4743 Interior Decorator IV :30. 1984 (Box 59)
        - 1032. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 4663 Interior Decorator I/Tag :30. 1984 (Box 59)
        - 1033. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 4743 Interior Decorator IV :30. 1984 (Box 59)
        - 1034. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 4641 ID vers. 2 :10. 1984 (Box 59)
      - Endust (continued), 1984-1986 (Box 60)
        - 1035. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 3563 Interior Decorator II :30. 1984 (Box 60)
        - 1036. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5783 Decorator V/New Demo :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1037. Marschalk. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 0473 Checkmate Rev. :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1038. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5803 Decorator IV/New Demo :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1039. Endust. Decorator V :20; Decorator V :10. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1040. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN Decorator IV/New Demo :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1041. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5803 Decorator IV/New Demo :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1042. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 1503 Interior Decorator :30; NMEN 4733 Interior Decorator II/New Lemon :30; BMEN 4641 ID Vers. 2 :10. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1043. Laurence Charles and Free. Endust. BMEN 5771 Decorator V/ID :10; BMEN 5762 Decorator V/20 :20; BMEN5793 Decorator V/ABC :30. 1985 (Box 60)
        - 1044. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6933 Interior Decorator Vii :30. 1986 (Box 60)
        - 1045. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6143 Interior Decorator VIII Rev. :30. 1986 (Box 60)
        - 1046. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6942 Interior Decorator Vii :20. 1986 (Box 60)
        - 1047. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5842 Interior Decorator VI B :20; BMEN 5831 Interior Decorator VI B Alt. :10. 1986 (Box 60)
        - 1048. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 60)
        - 1049. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6143 Interior Decorator VIII :30. 1986 (Box 60)
      - Endust (continued), 1986-1988 (Box 61)
        - 1050. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. Interior Decorator VI": BMEN 6893 Alt.3 :30; BMEN 6912 Alt. :20; BMEN 6925 Alt :15. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1051. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5842 Interior Decorator VI B :20; BMEN 5831 Interior Decorator VI B Alt. :10. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1052. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6103 Letters :30. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1053. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6143 Interior Decorator VIII :30. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1054. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6993 Intro/Step 2 :30. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1055. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. 9-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1056. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 5823 Interior Decorator VI B :30. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1057. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6942 Interior Decorator VII :20. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1058. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6103 Letters :30. 1986 (Box 61)
        - 1059. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 61)
        - 1060. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Endust. Step 2; BMEN 6183 Clean & Polish w/ Super Rev. 2 :30. 1987 (Box 61)
        - 1061. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6153 Letters-Wax Build Up Rev.4 :30. 1987 (Box 61)
        - 1062. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 7213 Wax Build Up :30. 1987 (Box 61)
        - 1063. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 6143 Interior Decorator VIII Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 61)
        - 1064. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Endust. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 61)
        - 1065. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 8273 Peabody & Daughter/Chart :30. 1988 (Box 61)
      - Endust (continued), 1988-1991 (Box 62)
        - 1066. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 8253 Wax Build-up Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 62)
        - 1067. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 8253 Wax Build-up Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 62)
        - 1068. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Endust. Doug Cowan Presentation. 1988 (Box 62)
        - 1069. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 8273 Peabody & Daughter/Chart :30. 1988 (Box 62)
        - 1070. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 9413 Cartoon :30. 1988 (Box 62)
        - 1071. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN9363 cartoon :30; BMEN 9363 Cartoon Alt. Track :30; BMEN 9383 Fable :30. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1072. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 9325 Peabody & Daughter :15. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1073. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. Cartoon :15. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1074. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 8293 Peabody & Daughter/Chart/Finger :30. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1075. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 9325 Peabody & Daughter :15. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1076. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN9425 Cartoon :15; BMEN 9432 Cartoon :20. 1989 (Box 62)
        - 1077. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEQ 0013 Cartoon-Hand :30; BMBJ Cartoon-Cat :15. 1990 (Box 62)
        - 1078. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 9425 Cartoon :15. 1990 (Box 62)
        - 1079. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 9425 Cartoon :15. 1990 (Box 62)
        - 1080. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 0495 Cartoon/Parrot :15; BMEN 0503 Cartoon/Parrot :30. 1990 (Box 62)
        - 1081. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Endust. BMEN 0503 Cartoon Parrot :30. 1991 (Box 62)
      - Mr. Muscle, 1975-1977 (Box 63)
        - 1082. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 4123 Main Street; BMMZ 5163 Married Man :30 each. 1975 (Box 63)
        - 1083. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 5203 Davies :30. 1975 (Box 63)
        - 1084. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 5213 Kilby :30. 1975 (Box 63)
        - 1085. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 6563 Less Fumes Generic :30. 1976 (Box 63)
        - 1086. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 6543 Less Dumes :30. Undated (Box 63)
        - 1087. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 6383 T Shirt Rev. :30. 1976 (Box 63)
        - 1088. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 6543 Less Fumes-New Cut. 1976 (Box 63)
        - 1089. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 6403 Toll Free :30. 1976 (Box 63)
        - 1090. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7843 Nighttime/Drudge :30. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1091. Mr. Muscle. So Dirty/MJ; So Dirty/Bibi. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1092. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7883 Nite/Fumes. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1093. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7873 Nighttime/F/D/ Rev. :30. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1094. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7713 So Dirty; BMMZ 7723 So Dirty Alt. :30 Each. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1095. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7823 MY Muscle/N/Drudge. 1977 (Box 63)
        - 1096. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 7743 So Dirty/MJ :30. 1977 (Box 63)
      - Mr. Muscle (continued), 1979-1993 (Box 64)
        - 1097. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. BMZZ 8923 Nancy :30. 1979 (Box 64)
        - 1098. Charles Inc. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 8913 Just Wipe; BMMZ 8903 Mr. Muscle. Mr. Muscle. Undated (Box 64)
        - 1099. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMZZ 9953 Nancy Rev. 1 :30. Undated (Box 64)
        - 1100. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. Our Muscle Rev.3 :30; Can't Beat It Re. 3 :30; Muscle men Rev.3 :30. 1981 (Box 64)
        - 1101. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. Muscle men Vers.2 :30. 1981 (Box 64)
        - 1102. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 1013 Our Muscle :30. 1982 (Box 64)
        - 1103. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 1993 Muscle men :30; BMMZ 1013 Our Muscle :30. 1982 (Box 64)
        - 1104. Laurence Charles and Free. Daniel & Charles. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 1013 Our Muscle :30. 1982 (Box 64)
        - 1105. Bristol Myers. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 3043 Animated Character :30. Undated (Box 64)
        - 1106. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Mr. Muscle. BMMZ 4113 Drudge II Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 64)
      - Renuzit, 1982-1984
        - 1107. Renuzit. fresh N' Wet Tested Vers. 1982 (Box 64)
        - 1108. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFD 3053 Fresh N' Wet :05 Tag. 1983 (Box 64)
        - 1109. Bristol Myers. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFD 3039 Fresh N' Wet Vs. Dry/non-new (Messy) :30. 1983 (Box 64)
        - 1110. Drackett Co. Bristol Myers. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFD 3151 6 Cans BB :10 Silent. 1983 (Box 64)
        - 1111. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Bristol Myers. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFG 3131 Fresh N' Wet Vs. Dry/new :10; BMFD 3141 Fresh N' Wet Vs. Dry/non-new":10. 1983 (Box 64)
        - 1112. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1984 (Box 64)
      - Renuzit (continued), 1985-1986 (Box 65)
        - 1113. Broadcast Arts. Renuzit. :10. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1114. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommate. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1115. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommate. BMRM 5063 Babilloney :30; BMRM 5073 High Tech Alt. :30; BMRM 5083 Song (Fish odor) :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1116. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Adjustable. BMRM 5033 Newlywed Alt Rev. I :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1117. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommate. BMRM 5083 Song (Fish Odor) :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1118. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommate. BMRM 5013 Song/Alt I :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1119. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFD 5313 Talking Can Rev2 :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1120. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRm 5033 Breakthrough :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1121. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit. Fresh N' Dry BMFD 5293 Talking Can :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1122. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 5043 60 Days/Vers.2 :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1123. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 5013 Song/Alt.1 :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1124. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 5013 Song/Alt.II :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1125. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 5013 Song/Alt.1 :30; BMRM 5013 Song/Alt.II :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1126. Laurence Charles and Free. Drackett Co. Renuzit Adjustable. BMRS 5043 House :30; BMRS 5053 Quartet Pool out :30. 1985 (Box 65)
        - 1127. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Reel. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 65)
        - 1128. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6173 Hunk :31; BMRM 6163 Married Women :31; BMRM 6183 Don't Tell My Husband :30. 1986 (Box 65)
      - Renuzit (continued), 1986-1987 (Box 66)
        - 1129. Original Roommate Exploratory. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1130. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6343 Hunk W/X-Ray Core :30. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1131. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Fresh And Dry. BMFD 6373 It's Superior :30; BMFD 6383 Hit By an Odor/EFX Vers. :30. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1132. Drackett Co. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6343 Hunk w/X-Ray Core Alt. :30. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1133. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM Hunk :15. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1134. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6281 Hunk Tease Rev. :10. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1135. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6405 Hunk :15. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1136. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1137. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6153 :31. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1138. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Fresh And Dry. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1139. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit. BMRM 5063 Babillerey; BMRM 5073 High Tech. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1140. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 66)
        - 1141. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 66)
        - 1142. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 66)
        - 1143. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit. BMRM 7773 :30; BMRM 7785 :15. 1987 (Box 66)
        - 1144. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 7773 Betrayed ABC :30; BMRM 7785 Betrayed ABC :15. 1987 (Box 66)
      - Renuzit (continued), 1987-1989 (Box 67)
        - 1145. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1146. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 7773 Betrayed ABC :30; BMRM 7785 Betrayed AbC :15; BMRM 7795 Cheated ABC :15. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1147. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 7763 Betrayed Too :30. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1148. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1149. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1150. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1151. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1152. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 7735 Conned :15. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1153. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 67)
        - 1154. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Roommates. Reel 2 of 2. 1988 (Box 67)
        - 1155. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 8815 Dark :15; BMRM 8855 More :15. 1988 (Box 67)
        - 1156. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 4 Spots. 1988 (Box 67)
        - 1157. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Roommates. Reel 1 of 2. 1988 (Box 67)
        - 1158. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Freshell. BMIR 9173 Fish Family/Non-New :30; BMIR 9185 Fish Family/Non-New :15. 1989 (Box 67)
        - 1159. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 9883 Dark.Line :30. 1989 (Box 67)
        - 1160. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 9883 Dark.Line :30. 1989 (Box 67)
        - 1161. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Renuzit Reel. 7 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 67)
      - Renuzit (continued), 1990-1993 (Box 68)
        - 1162. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Freshell. BMIR 0233 Not A Shell/Refill Tag :30. 1990 (Box 68)
        - 1163. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit. BMGN 0045 Pooping Up :15. 1990 (Box 68)
        - 1164. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Drackett Co. Renuzit Freshell. BMIR 0193 Not A Shell :30; BMIR 0205 Not A Shell/Continuity :15. 1990 (Box 68)
        - 1165. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit. BMZP 0093 Something Beautiful :30. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1166. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. Something Beautiful: BMZP 1163 :30; BMZP 1175 :15. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1167. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Professional Strength Windex. XYLC 1653 Emily; XYLC 1663 Sal/Professional Cleaning Service; XYLC 1673 92lb. Women. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1168. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 1963 Pastel Colors :30; BMRM 1975 Pastel Colors :15. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1169. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. BMZP 1205 Something Beautiful Rev. 1 :15. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1170. Bristol Myers Squibb. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 68)
        - 1171. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. New Shapes-Blonde": BMZP 2313 :30; BMZP 2335 :15. 1992 (Box 68)